<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Elect Socialist for Scarborough Centre</title>
    <subtitle></subtitle>
    <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca"/>
    <updated>2022-11-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca</id>
    <author>
        <name>Claudia R</name>
    </author>
    <entry>
        <title>Ontario Education Workers, Must Struggle to Win</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/ontario-education-workers-must-struggle-to-win/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/ontario-education-workers-must-struggle-to-win/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The enemy ‘Thug Ford’ is a viciously reactionary but erratic and incompetent regime headed by a blustering buffoon. This fight can serve as a beacon to workers and hard pressed communities to find hope, take courage and be part of a sweeping fight back. The demand to “Dump Thug Ford with A General Strike” is rising out of necessity.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Jordan Peterson, A Snake Oil Expert?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/jordan-peterson-a-snake-oil-expert/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/jordan-peterson-a-snake-oil-expert/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
During my early years, I was really interested in clinical psychology. I would often spend my evening watching his lectures and learning from his approach to investigating and solving complex social and psychological issues. After a while though, his approach to understanding social problems were narrow and limited - particularly his tendency to blame the victim and empathize with those in control was starting to be obnoxious.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Jews Who Leave Israel for Good</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/jews-who-leave-israel-for-good/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/jews-who-leave-israel-for-good/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Every Jewish immigrant that enters Israel is unwittingly taking part in a continual referendum on its chances of survival. But many of those who enter Israel also choose to leave it. Nearly, half of those who emigrated in 2003 from the US went back, rare statistics not covered in the mainstream media.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Treatment of Migrant Workers in Ontario</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/treatment-of-migrant-workers-in-ontario/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/treatment-of-migrant-workers-in-ontario/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
My employment experience exposes the systematic flaws that needed to make employees of my kind safer at work places. The Ontario Occupational Health and Safety body along with Labour Relations Board is inadequate to protect employees from workplace violence. The notion of expectation that Union is to protect employees from bullying, harassment and discrimination is only as good as any April fool pranks.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Slaves in Uniform with Big Dreams</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/slaves-in-uniform-with-big-dreams/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/slaves-in-uniform-with-big-dreams/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Big corporate criminals in coat, suit and tie behind the screens do more harm to workers than the COVID itself. Those parasites such as CEO John Campbell do not work or contribute to economy in any meaningful way but thrives by sucking the blood of employees. Even at the heights of pandemic killing workers, profit was the main priority for the secret scum family. Workers must stand up to the domestic terrorism or else our children would become homeless in the richest nations.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Victory in Difference; Not Numbers</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/victory-in-difference-not-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/victory-in-difference-not-numbers/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Thank you to my people of Scarborough. Our victory is work in progress. I am proud of our collective achievement against the status quo and so you should be too.Thank you Scarborough Tenants Union, Acorn Canada, This Time in History, Municipal Socialist Alliance, Socialist Action, Stop the Split and to all those endorsed, volunteered and stood in solidarity. We moved the immovable, please see the full statement.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Corruption and Destruction of NDP Trust</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/corruption-and-destruction-of-ndp-trust/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/corruption-and-destruction-of-ndp-trust/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
For class conscious voters, New Democratic Party (NDP) aka Canadian labour party was the only source of hope for democracy. However, the hope was shattered through executive committee of the British Columbia (BC) NDP party decision to disqualify a candidate recommended by its members. The radical decision of NDP executive reflected the true disconnection between the interest of working people and the party leadership ambitions.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>In Politics, Elect Policy; Not Personality</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/in-politics-elect-policy-not-personality/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/in-politics-elect-policy-not-personality/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Politics is often thought of as a complicated subject but its not. If we apply common sense instead of feelings, it would be crystal clear and simple to understand. Politics is a manipulative blame game of power and greed without responsibility in western society.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What Drives Me to Fight for Change?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/what-drives-me-to-fight-for-change/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/what-drives-me-to-fight-for-change/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Most often, we strive to fight against the system that degrades humanity but at some point, we lose energy and motivation to fight. Thats the way our status quo system is designed so no change can happen from the grassroots. Working class people have no choice but to fight till the end or surrender to the status quo.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Barrier to Democracy, Status Quo Benefiters</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/barrier-to-democracy-status-quo-benefiters/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/barrier-to-democracy-status-quo-benefiters/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The housing is a crisis situation in Toronto. Average wait time to receive a rent geared to income housing in the big city is 10 years. Sadly, poverty does not wait that long but the status quo does not care. If one was to ask, why does things get worse year after year, the answer is simple. Those who represent the people have no interest in addressing the root cause of the problem such as poverty.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Purpose of LinkedIn Today</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-purpose-of-linkedin-today/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-purpose-of-linkedin-today/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
This platform is essentially a capitalist culture app, a market for the trade of organizational snake oils, disguised as &quot;networking.&quot; The fact that we&#39;re able to create meaningful bonds and even organize on here is testament to how resilient we can collectively be, even amidst this sea of classist exploitation. And that fills me with immense hope. Justice belongs in ALL spaces including LinkedIn regardless of what the status quo enforcers say.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Canada Must Rise to the Challenge</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/canada-must-rise-to-the-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-29T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/canada-must-rise-to-the-challenge/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Canada is at a crossroads. We are facing multiple pressing challenges that need immediate action: The ongoing impact of Covid-19, inflation gnawing at stagnant paycheques, a health care system squeezed to the limit, the climate crisis, and the ongoing need to dismantle colonialism and systemic racism. An excerpt from Centre for Policy Alternatives.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Have Honest Conversations with Children</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/have-honest-conversations-with-children/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/have-honest-conversations-with-children/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
If wars are so bad, why does it still exist? Adults are smart enough to sort out the differences unlike kids in the playground; yet, commit the most atrocities crimes against innocent children, women and the elderly. Honest answer would not only help the child but also the parent to become better community members.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why Democracy is Failing in the West?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/why-democracy-is-failing-in-the-west/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/why-democracy-is-failing-in-the-west/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
People agree that democracy is failing is the west without any reservations. But, the reasoning of why decimate the debate even before the start. If one was to ask, do you know your city councillor in your ward or member of parliament? Most voters would respond yes but in reality, voters barely know the candidate name.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Trails of Nuclear propaganda</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/trails-of-nuclear-propaganda/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/trails-of-nuclear-propaganda/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Trails of nuclear propaganda from Iraq to Ukraine. When we come to realize that saviours of democracy are the destroyers of peace, our heartaches. We are not standing on a level ground to be able to see everything objectively. Therefore, it is vital for us to question everything. The corporate America have no interest in preserving human rights but profit only.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Labour History, more Important than Nutrition</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/labour-history-more-important-than-nutrition/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/labour-history-more-important-than-nutrition/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Most of us are graduating from college and universities with no knowledge of surplus value of labour. Read that again, let that sink in. We must not stop learning even after school but that exactly what happens when some enter for profit school system. Schools controlled by the capitalist class replaced history, music and arts with fake career courses that ensure students cannot think outside the scope of profit.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>No Tech for Apartheid, Google Employees</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/no-tech-for-apartheid-google-employees/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/no-tech-for-apartheid-google-employees/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Google Workers Push for Cancellation of Secretive $1.2B Project with Israel - Sep 1, 2022 - A national day of action is planned next Thursday as protests grow against Google&#39;s secretive $1.2 billion program known as Project #Nimbus, which will provide advanced #artificialintelligence tools to the Israeli government and military.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>COVID Death Profit Using Science</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/covid-death-profit-using-science/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/covid-death-profit-using-science/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
As the wave of COVID struck, the most poorest parts of the earth experienced the highest deaths. While the loss of lives were unbearable, most ugliest things were COVID profiteers. Some millionaires embarrassingly returned the COVID benefits in the developed countries while big corporations tweaked the numbers to make sure the extreme covid profits does not create unusual attention.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Corporate Media and the Manipulation</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/corporate-media-and-the-manipulation/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/corporate-media-and-the-manipulation/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Corporate media have mastered the art of manipulation to uphold injustice and status quo throughout the century. Today, one cannot deny the fact that not reading news makes us uninformed while reading news keeps us misinformed. Where do we go from here?

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>War Statistics from 1945 to 2001</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/war-statistics-from-1945-to-2001/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/war-statistics-from-1945-to-2001/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Wars launched between 1945 - 2001, US 81% other countries 19%. Stats do not lie. Imperial wars from Iraq to Ukraine is a disaster for humanity. Dismantling United States military complex is the only way to feed the poor and bring world peace. Sadly, that is not even possible anymore.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Financial Facts on Canadian Prisons</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/financial-facts-on-canadian-prisons/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/financial-facts-on-canadian-prisons/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Total (federal, provincial and municipal) public spending on criminal justice in Canada per year is about $20 billion. (The Parliamentary Budget Officer did a careful breakdown in 2011-12). About 70% of this spending is provincial/municipal. The total amounts to about $550 in taxes per person in Canada per year. An excerpt from John Howard Society.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Legal Prescription to Eliminate Crimes</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/legal-prescription-to-eliminate-crimes/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/legal-prescription-to-eliminate-crimes/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Most people in Toronto are concerned about rising violent crimes in the city. Unfortunately, crime is not the sole responsibility of the police but collective responsibility of everyone in the city. As people of Scarborough, we can not only work toward eliminating crimes but make our communities safer for everyone. We just have to make the punishment fit the crime. The recipe is simple to execute but our status quo politicians will not do it. The ruling class is only interested in using crime as a weapon to further exploit working and the poor people of our city.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Double Genocide of Ceylon Tamils</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/double-genocide-of-ceylon-tamils/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/double-genocide-of-ceylon-tamils/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
A misconception as common as it is incorrect, is that the weeklong violence of Black July was retaliation for the LTTE’s killing of 13 soldiers. In fact, what took place was not a spontaneous outburst of mob violence; rather, it was a systematic and intentional GoSL-sponsored genocide.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Either Stand for Justice or Support Injustice</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/either-stand-for-justice-or-support-injustice/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/either-stand-for-justice-or-support-injustice/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
We must be brave and bold to demand justice. Corporate puppets always find a way to liberalize justice movements, notably Black Lives Matter. Instead of calling out the bread crumbs of slavery, traitors of working class bullied the working class movement. Police are tools of the ruling class to maintain the status quo for the owner class. Regardless of the environment, if diversity, equity and inclusion efforts are separate from the pursuit of justice - do not join.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Poverty, Crime and the Insanity</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/poverty-crime-and-the-insanity/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/poverty-crime-and-the-insanity/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
We all know that doing the same thing over and over will not lead to different outcome in life but when it come to politics, we do just that. We keep electing the same political parties to maintain the status quo and then get disappointed of our actions. Our education and healthcare, the most vital services cannot be improved when de-funded; however, we expect to improve nonetheless.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Church, Government and the Corporation</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/church-government-and-the-corporation/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/church-government-and-the-corporation/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
There is great relationship between churches, corporations and governments of all types. Under all conditions, they not go against each other. Either they stand together or remain silent to support each other. All three are perfectly united evil friends who make sure masses are controlled in a way to protect the interest of the ruling class.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Cruel Nature of Faith Culture</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/cruel-nature-of-faith-culture/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/cruel-nature-of-faith-culture/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The faith systems exist to protect the ruling class. Of course, we do not have control over some things in life; however, we do have control over many things including politics. The faith system regardless of religion work together with the ruling powers to justify the status quo and protect the corrupted politics. When corrupted politicians make collective decision to exploit people for profit, churches sell the myth that it is god’s fault.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Campaign for Socialism and Democracy in NDP</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-campaign-for-socialism-and-democracy-in-ndp/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-campaign-for-socialism-and-democracy-in-ndp/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
After nearly four years of the most regressive, incompetent and corrupt Ontario government in decades, opinions polls show the Doug Ford Conservatives leading and the New Democratic mired in third place, well behind Liberals, on the eve of June 2 provincial election.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Alternative to Pandemic-Era Housing Crisis</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/alternative-to-pandemic-era-housing-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/alternative-to-pandemic-era-housing-crisis/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Whether a couple is planning to settle down or a family is seeking a place to raise kids in the province, they are sure to feel the heat in the Canadian housing market. The question: ‘How did we get here?’ often leads to inconclusive answers and simply pointing a finger at the easiest target. The predatory nature of housing market big players means they have no interest in addressing the needs of the people. For them, housing is a commodity designed to make shareholders happy. Actually, the housing market is doing very well to meet its mandates – funneling wealth upwards.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why NDP Support Apartheid Crimes?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/why-ndp-support-apartheid-crimes/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/why-ndp-support-apartheid-crimes/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The Federal New Democratic Party (NDP) not only lost the mainstream elections in Canada since early 1990 but also lost its roots to serve the working people completely. Of course, corporate extremists eroded unions, labours and labour party but that is not an an excuse to tangle in internal politics to silence labour and human rights activists within the NDP. Sadly, NDP proved it has no interest in standing up for human rights inside or outside the borders through dropping an elected candidate in Vaughan.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Inflation Crisis or Economical Scam?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/inflation-crisis-or-economical-scam/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/inflation-crisis-or-economical-scam/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
COVID indicates that inflation is a not a natural cause but a planned economic disaster to make the rich get rich while poor get poor. Instead of being complicit, there are solutions to the problem that status quo leaders do not want people to know. The pandemic have transferred the wealth upwards and proved that the whole banking system is just a scam.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Green-washing While Earth on Fire</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/green-washing-while-earth-on-fire/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/green-washing-while-earth-on-fire/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Big corporations from oil to tech continue to green wash the economy for the purpose of more tax dollar extraction. We see that everyday on the television but somehow we are customized to accept the gimmick as real solution. Real solution include raising the standards of living for the people but that would upset the profit margins so green washing the way to go.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Brand Politics Legitimize Dictatorship</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/brand-politics-legitimize-dictatorship/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/brand-politics-legitimize-dictatorship/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
In Canada, we have four mainstream political parties but only two ruled almost the entire time. The red liberal lies and the blue conservative crooks. Although both parties appears to have difficult political platform, in reality, both are just the same with altered words. If we analyze the decisions of each party historically, we would be shocked to know that both parties are just the same brand packaged under different names. Sadly, Obama dropped more bombs, killed more people and replaced legitimate leaders in third world countries than than Trump did.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Key Facts About Residential Schools</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/key-facts-about-residential-schools/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/key-facts-about-residential-schools/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Residential schools were government-sponsored religious schools that were established to assimilate Indigenous children into Euro-Canadian culture. Although the first residential facilities were established in New France, the term usually refers to schools established after 1880. Residential schools were created by Christian churches and the Canadian government as an attempt to both educate and convert Indigenous youth and to assimilate them into Canadian society. However, the schools disrupted lives and communities, causing long-term problems among Indigenous peoples. The last residential school closed in 1996. An excerpt from The Canadian Encyclopedia.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Confronting Genocide in Canada Regretfully</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/confronting-genocide-in-canada-regretfully/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/confronting-genocide-in-canada-regretfully/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The Canadian Museum for Human Rights recognizes that the colonial experience in Canada, from first contact to the present, constitutes genocide against Indigenous peoples. The Indian residential school system was one key component of this genocide.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Inflation Gimmick in Status Quo Politics</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/inflation-gimmick-in-status-quo-politics/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/inflation-gimmick-in-status-quo-politics/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Instead of throwing around fancy terms, we must stop and define all the buzz words. What is inflation? where does it begin? Is it caused by nature? Who wins and who loses? Answering the four questions would set one on the right path to realize inflation is just an economical gimmick to justify the status quo. The buzz word inflation is political forgery to protect the ruling class.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Corporate Misuse of Canadian Tax Revenue</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/corporate-misuse-of-canadian-tax-revenue/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/corporate-misuse-of-canadian-tax-revenue/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Despite previous assurances that it would not result in additional costs, a new report says the TTC will spend millions of dollars more on fare collection each year by using the Presto smartcard instead of tickets, tokens and passes. Skeleton in the closet is the breach of privacy and violent enforcement of the broken fare system. An excerpt from Toronto Star.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pandemic CEOs and Fake Guru Market</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/pandemic-ceos-and-fake-guru-market/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/pandemic-ceos-and-fake-guru-market/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Regardless of political standing, we can all agree that pandemic have exposed many issues in our society. One the core issue was unjust wages that resulted in people earning less and losing more through the pandemic; meanwhile, those at the top get richer. The status quo argument was that CEOs earn their salary but poor workers are not. The conversation took a 360 turn after pandemic where front line workers were working the hardest under dangerous conditions while CEOs were watching Netflix.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Vaccine Mandates Unite Left and Right</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/vaccine-mandates-unite-left-and-right/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/vaccine-mandates-unite-left-and-right/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
For long time, people on the left and right were divided; however, pandemic closed the gap. Ruling class is on the edge of falling into the ocean; yet, holding onto the greed of wealth by funding the paramilitary structures and wars. Regardless, vaccine mandates elegantly united the left and right in a way that no one have ever imagined. Mask is not the problem, the slavery wage is that both sides now agree except the ruling class.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Lies, Deception and the Romance</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-lies-deception-and-the-romance/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-lies-deception-and-the-romance/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
When we ask, why most people dislike politics, the answer is pretty obvious. No one likes being lied or asked to believe a false reality. Therefore, working people shy away from politics; which reflects in the statistics that only a small percentage of eligible working people actually vote in local politics. If all the workers actually caste vote, status quo will change in a heartbeat, that is the great nightmare of ruling class.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Omicron Crisis: Workers&#39; on the Frontline</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/omicron-crisis-workers-on-the-frontline/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/omicron-crisis-workers-on-the-frontline/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
On Tuesday, January 11, 2022 at 7p.m. over 300 front-line workers from coast to coast joined a Zoom Conference in response to the Omicron crisis. The conference host, Justice for Workers Organization, was overwhelmed by the participation and passion of frontline workers from variety of sectors, including health, education, transportation, agriculture and newly emerging freelance/ gig workers. The conference included special guest Ontario New Democratic Party (ONDP) Member of Provincial Parliament (MPP) Peggy Sattler from London West, guest speaker Dr. Naheed Dosani, and observers from the Migrant Rights Network, along with Ontario Federation of Labour (OFL).

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Who Controls Toronto - People or Developers?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/who-controls-toronto-people-or-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/who-controls-toronto-people-or-developers/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
In the 2018 Toronto Municipal Election, 34% of all campaign contributions came from people with ties to the development industry. Many important decisions on the right to housing are being influenced by these donors, to the detriment of regular people in Toronto. An excerpt from Acorn Canada Research.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Climate Crisis: Eco Socialism or Extinction</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/climate-crisis-eco-socialism-or-extinction/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/climate-crisis-eco-socialism-or-extinction/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
On September 24, 2021 over a thousand environmental activists took to the streets of Toronto as part of a worldwide climate strike. The event, organized by Fridays for Future Toronto, shouted “Save Our Planet” loud and clear. The protesters, including students, workers, women and children, walked together to end violence against the nature, the planet and humanity.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Do not Abandon the Vulnerable. Act Now!</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/do-not-abandon-the-vulnerable-act-now/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/do-not-abandon-the-vulnerable-act-now/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
On Saturday, September 18, 2021, a small crowd rallied in Toronto at the Yonge and Dundas intersection calling for an end to discriminatory funding to ODSP and OW programs. POOF Protecting ODSP OW Funding is a community group striving to end Homelessness and Poverty for people on ODSP, Ontario Disability Support Program and OW, Ontario Works benefits. The event organizer, Isabella Gamk, said that people on ODSP and OW benefits are abandoned by all 3 levels of Canadian Government and left to fend for themselves with less than a livable income support. Sadly, the City of Toronto has no tangible plans to help marginalized people living on a poverty income.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Report on ACORN-led Protest Against Big Bank Fees</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/report-on-acorn-led-protest-against-big-bank-fees/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/report-on-acorn-led-protest-against-big-bank-fees/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
On July 13, 2021 Socialist Action members joined in solidarity with 40 ACORN activists to protest the policies of the big banks. The Toronto action was part of a cross-country set of rallies to demand lowering NSF (Not Sufficient Funds) penalties from $45 to $10, waiving the minimum bank balance of $4000 to end discriminatory fees and stopping the financing of predatory lenders like EasyFinancial. In the heart of downtown Toronto, the march for fair banking touched major financial institutions in the Bay and King street zone.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Destruction of English Language</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/destruction-of-english-language/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/destruction-of-english-language/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
English, a 1500 years old German language, British adapted and universalized through European colonizations. Fluency of English or any language is unrelated to human Intelligence, through socially constructed illusion as such.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Housing is Essential: No Covid Evictions</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/housing-is-essential-no-covid-evictions/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/housing-is-essential-no-covid-evictions/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Thursday, May 27 at 7 pm, “No COVID Evictions” with Rob McBean of Socialist Action and ACORN. Host: Elizabeth Byce. Discussants: Maryanna Lewycky, East York ACORN, founding member of CAPREIT Tenants’ Union, Euridice Baumgarten, Tenant Worker, Federation of Metro Tenants’ Associations, and Kiri Vadivelu, Scarborough ACORN, founder of Scarborough Tenants’ Union.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Labour day with Kurdistan Community at Thomason’s Park</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/labour-day-with-kurdistan-community-at-thomason-s-park/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/labour-day-with-kurdistan-community-at-thomason-s-park/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Labour day celebration with Kurdistan community in Thomason’s Park, Scarborough. Unlike any other celebration, labour day bring all workers across the communities together in the same spirit. Workers build the country; not corporations. Thats why union of working people always strive to protect the communities everyday as oppose corporate green-washing for media coverage to mask everyday exploitation of labour and resources.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Rise and Fall of Great America</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/rise-and-fall-of-great-america/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/rise-and-fall-of-great-america/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
In most developing countries, American dream is still the ultimate achievement of true happiness and satisfaction. But, those who are already in North America and hostage to financial institutions argue that a great American nightmare. When you build American Empire using blood and sweat of working class Americans by looting the planet under the pretext of democracy, that is nothing but armed robbery of world peace.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Kick the Can, Down the Road</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/kick-the-can-down-the-road/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/kick-the-can-down-the-road/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
There are many strategies to solve real problems rather than to let them persist. A primary method employed in politics is kicking the can down the road instead of reaching for the solution. Every problem is an opportunity for profit under capitalism. Hence, elected officials are loyal to the profit of big corporations than the needs of the people.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Who Votes in Municipal Elections?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/who-votes-in-municipal-elections/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/who-votes-in-municipal-elections/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Who votes in Toronto municipal elections? This landmark study identifies significant variations in voter turnout among eligible voters across the city’s 44 wards and 140 official neighbourhoods over the past three civic elections of 2003, 2006 and 2010. We are especially interested in identifying how an area’s proportion of immigrants, visible minorities, tenants and its median household income impacts voter turnout. We conclude that Toronto has a distinctly uneven geography and demography of municipal voting. An excerpt from MayTree Policy Research.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Will Smith Slapped Chris Rock Nonsense</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/will-smith-slapped-chris-rock-nonsense/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/will-smith-slapped-chris-rock-nonsense/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Most people found out about the elite hand picked clown award show after Will slapped Chris. Why the heck the entire social media is talking about the nonsense? Well, elites know how to play the game. Millionaires played their usual trick to turn the attention of pay-cheque hostages on them.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Three Pillars of Social System</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/three-pillars-of-social-system/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/three-pillars-of-social-system/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Based on the classification system, RULING CLASS does not benefit directly from the wars. However, ruling class require expressing the interest of the OWNER CLASS to remain in power. For instance, Deputy Prime minister of Canada, Chrystia Freeland attending Ukraine support rally to carry Ukraine-Nazi flag is an expression of owner class interest; instead of anti-poverty flag.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What is Wrong with Our Society?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/what-is-wrong-with-our-society/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/what-is-wrong-with-our-society/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Nothing. Our society is fine. We are the problem. All of our actions have have consequences. That social, economical and political conflicts as result of our direct actions and inactions. We must stop using violence and start peaceful means to communicate with one another.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Cut the Chase, Get to the Point</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/cut-the-chase-get-to-the-point/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/cut-the-chase-get-to-the-point/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Most people are afraid to engage in difficult conversations. Because humans are driven to be at peace and harmony by default; not at conflict. That is a blessing and a curse at the same time.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Eradicate Zionists to Save Humanity</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/eradicate-zionists-to-save-humanity/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/eradicate-zionists-to-save-humanity/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
As progress is the real purpose, human rights activists including Malcolm X fought for free speech and to eradicate slavery for the good of humanity. However, Zionist Jews were able to use lies and deception to destroy democracy through creating illegitimate laws to ruin free speech.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Real Enemy of Free Speech</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-real-enemy-of-free-speech/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-real-enemy-of-free-speech/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Free speech is the cornerstone of democracy. Whether our political stand is on the right, left or centre, defending the right to free speech is the most important civil duty. Over the years, the right to free speech has been eliminated using variety of legal apparatus.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Corporate Welfare Bums</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-corporate-welfare-bums/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-corporate-welfare-bums/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The corporate welfare bums are also knowns as capitalist death cult is a threat to health and wellbeing of all labour. A death cult can be understood as vicious, dark and evil chain of thinking, acting and behaving to destruct natural life cycles. Bank is an example of structural capitalism to colonize labour wealth at the expense of humanity to benefit corporate bums.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>United Snakes Keep Americans Broke</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/united-snakes-keep-americans-broke/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/united-snakes-keep-americans-broke/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The corporate welfare system implemented by the CIA ensures that American tax dollars do not go into the hands of people. By keeping the money in the hands of big corporations, America can continue to dominate the world economy. Sadly, the economical dominance must also be backed with the ability to commit political violence in the name of war for peace to maintain the status quo.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>American Strategy to Mobile Wealth Upwards</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/american-strategy-to-mobile-wealth-upwards/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/american-strategy-to-mobile-wealth-upwards/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
What separate America from previous empires is the economical strategy to mobilize wealth upwards, consistently. World economy contribute to the wealth of America through making all transactions in American dollars. After the fall of British Pounds, American dollar is considered to be the most reliable currency; that directly correspond to the military capacity of America to inflict violence against any sovereign nation.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Vaccination Save Corporate Lives</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/vaccination-save-corporate-lives/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-17T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/vaccination-save-corporate-lives/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Scientific studies were highly respected in academic world due to the potential to save humanity. However, profit driven science do not have the same principles. When the true motivation of humanity is replaced with profit, science is nothing but another marketing scheme.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Theft without Stigma, Society without Answers</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/theft-without-stigma-society-without-answers/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/theft-without-stigma-society-without-answers/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The surplus value is an excess profit of wealth produced by the labour. Under capitalism, 100 percent of the profit goes directly to the owner. But, under communism, 100 percent of the profit goes directly to the government. When a society is either only capitalism or communism, the catastrophe is created. Individuals are greedy and power is corrupt; therefore, society suffers.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Greed is Ugly, Lets not Glorify</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/greed-is-ugly-lets-not-glorify/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/greed-is-ugly-lets-not-glorify/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Greed is an intense and selfish desire for something, particularly wealth, power or status. However, most people tend not to criticize the greed of another due to potential jealousy portrayals. Interestingly, jealousy is manageable but greed is not. For the purpose of simplicity, greed can be understood as excessive desire based on the context of survival necessity to co-exist within given society.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Good Samaritans are the Escape Goats</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/good-samaritans-are-the-escape-goats/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/good-samaritans-are-the-escape-goats/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Early pioneers of democratic system really had good intention to preserve the humanity; however, the ruling class did not. Political rulers seize power using variety of social manipulation in order to serve the few and themselves in the process. Regretfully, lies are manufactured, humanity is sacrificed and people are divided in the most free world.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Faith Business in the Name of Christ</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/faith-business-in-the-name-of-christ/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/faith-business-in-the-name-of-christ/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The great old saying is “money talks, bullshit walks”. The statement is so brief often get overlooked after the initial conversation. But, the four words shall not only be memorized but must be applied on day to day interactions with authorities should one concerned about knowing the truth of any subject matter. All religious services; particularly churches operate based on donations; one shall follow the money to the destination.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Circus of Hitler NAZI to NATO America</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/circus-of-hitler-nazi-to-nato-america/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/circus-of-hitler-nazi-to-nato-america/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Although Europe civilization was evolving much faster than other regions, the people of Germany were not immune from political misfortunes. Since average household is already in constant battle to make ends meet while managing social politics within the family, the eager to participate in the community welfare is the last option for many. Hence, the lack of community participation from contributing members creates a vacuum for illegitimate political leadership. Unfortunately, the fascist leaders often the real opportunists to benefit from social, economical and political crisis.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>And then, They Came for Me, Journalist</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/and-then-they-came-for-me-journalist/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/and-then-they-came-for-me-journalist/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The ethnic minority Tamils have been fighting for social, economical and political equality since the independence of Ceylon from British in 1947. The Northern part of Island was home to Tamils, a 15 percent population, while southern part was occupied by 80 percent Sinhalese; meanwhile, east and west were home to Muslim and other minorities.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Great Decline of Human Empathy in Society</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/great-decline-of-human-empathy-in-society/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/great-decline-of-human-empathy-in-society/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Empathy is a special trait of human species, the ability to understand and share the feelings of another irrespective of the circumstances. Accordingly to evolutionary psychology, the emotional intelligences of humans do have the capacity to imagine and connect with another even when the crisis is not seen, heard or experienced directly.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>No Pride in American Show Business</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/no-pride-in-american-show-business/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/no-pride-in-american-show-business/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
While most American friends of colour are proud about the nomination of first black woman Ketanji Brown Jackson to Supreme Court of United States, the great personal achievement may not translate into meaningful change for average Americans; basing on the recent history of show business in politics. Outside of media glamorization, there is nothing black about Obama, Harris or Jackson.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pandemic Exposure of Canadian Double Standards</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/pandemic-exposure-of-canadian-double-standards/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/pandemic-exposure-of-canadian-double-standards/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
As the COVID emergency slammed the brake on the world economy, a radical action was forced to protect the people. Unexpectedly, the impact of pandemic death toll driven lock downs coerced even the capitalist countries to roll out emergency assistance. Without a choice, Canadian liberal government rolled out temporary $2000 paycheque for all Canadians. The program made Liberal government to appear as the most radical left humanitarian government; but, the reality is the opposite.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Two Types of Negros - House and Field</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/two-types-of-negros-house-and-field/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/two-types-of-negros-house-and-field/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
“There were two kinds of slaves, the house Negro and the field Negro. The house Negroes--they lived in the house with master, they dressed pretty good, they ate good because they ate his food--what he left. They lived in the attic or the basement, but still they lived near their master; and they loved their master more than their master loved himself. They would give their life to save their master&#39;s house--quicker than the master would. If the master said, &quot;We got a good house here,&quot; the house Negro would say, &quot;Yeah, we got a good house here.&quot; Whenever the master said &quot;we,&quot; he said &quot;we.&quot; That&#39;s how you can tell a house Negro.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>American Eagle is on Guard for Thee</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/american-eagle-is-on-guard-for-thee/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/american-eagle-is-on-guard-for-thee/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Every empire in the history fought wars to steal but America has perfected the art of boosting the economy through war, consistently. For the credit of war driven economy, American corporations have looted the planet for profit because war is a profitable business. In order for the America to operate without loosing credibility, Hollywood maintained the status quo culture of violence through feeding lies to Americans and to those fans of American violence.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Expertise Method of Money Laundering</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/expertise-method-of-money-laundering/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/expertise-method-of-money-laundering/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Money laundering is a serious financial crime. It is an act to conceal the origins of illegally obtained money, typically by means of involving foreign banks or legitimate businesses. Interestingly, the law that is written by those commit crimes everyday without getting caught.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Hidden Truth About Financial Investment</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/hidden-truth-about-financial-investment/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/hidden-truth-about-financial-investment/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
As revolutionary economist and German philosopher , Karl Marxist is a harsh critique of capitalist economic system. As a humanitarian, he felt that the capitalist system is unsustainable model, cruel to humanity and evil that thrives on the organized violence against people. He advocated for better society that would preserve economy, humanity and planet; though his vision was never fully implemented in practice due to variety of conflicts. His prominent work “The Communist Manifesto” was even inspired his opponents to create “The Capitalist Manifesto” a copycat version.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Contribution of Jeffrey Epstein to Philanthropy</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/contribution-of-jeffrey-epstein-to-philanthropy/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/contribution-of-jeffrey-epstein-to-philanthropy/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
One primary reason American people are blind to injustice everywhere is because no one invaded America over a century. Instead of building relationship, American elites have been burning bridges internationally. Only way to have friendship with the elites of United States is to participate to commit crime against humanity such as philanthropy work; best defined as private pedophile projects (P3).

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What is Real Challenge in Democracy?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/what-is-real-challenge-in-democracy/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/what-is-real-challenge-in-democracy/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Elections in capitalist countries always risk that the majority employees will vote to end the income and wealth inequalities produced by capitalism. So capitalists buy parties, politicians, mass media, etc. It’s their self defense against real democracy. Memorize the line and repeat every time when the alarm clock goes.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Stand with Ukraine, Cancel the Debt</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/stand-with-ukraine-cancel-the-debt/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/stand-with-ukraine-cancel-the-debt/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The war mongering European Nations (EU) have been providing significant humanitarian aids but all come at significant cost under the carpet. All of the sentiment to support Ukraine is successfully rewarding the pockets of bankers in Europe and North America. Across the world, the voice to support Ukraine is genuine; however, financial industries have not waved any interest payment that could be used to support the people in crisis. World sympathy, particularly American sympathy is going to be too expensive for Ukraine people to bear in the aftermaths of war.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Progress of Brainwashing Culture in America</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/progress-of-brainwashing-culture-in-america/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/progress-of-brainwashing-culture-in-america/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The special vocabulary, greenwashing and greenscamming are reserved for corporations that acknowledge the importance of environment preservation, yet, continue to cultivate the predatory culture for profit. Big corporations have adequate financial resources at disposal to create bogus jobs in order to skim more public tax dollars from government.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Are You Still Paying Taxes to Monarchy?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/are-you-still-paying-taxes-to-monarchy/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/are-you-still-paying-taxes-to-monarchy/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The ancient voluntary taxation system was created to ensure all people have access to food, medicine and basic humanitarian needs. However, the corrupted kings used the tax dollars to organize military, protect monarchy and build tools to kill people. When people realized the misuse of hard earned dollars; people refused to pay taxes. What rational mind would pay money to kill innocent people?

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Stop Wars, De-fund Military Complex</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/stop-wars-de-fund-military-complex/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/stop-wars-de-fund-military-complex/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
According to War Statistics, America is the enemy of peace and prosperity everywhere. Those who live outside of United States knows more about America than actual Americans. When actor Will Smith slapped comedian Chris Rock on the stage, Americans debated while non Americans laughed and confirmed the truth about American culture. While Americans wave the flag and believe America as the symbol of peace, rest of the world disgusted at the reminder of all crime against humanity committed by American military.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Intelligence Drought of American Corporations</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/intelligence-drought-of-american-corporations/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/intelligence-drought-of-american-corporations/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Greed of corporate America to accumulate wealth for few while 80 percent of Americans fight for 20 percent of resources within American border is the beginning of greatest failures. After 2000 years of civilization, humans reached the moon, made nuclear bombs and installed puppet governments in every country or destroyed when refused; yet could not solve wealth inequality, homeless deaths and food shortages.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Radical Change is Necessary to Save Humanity</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/radical-change-is-necessary-to-save-humanity/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/radical-change-is-necessary-to-save-humanity/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
No one would disagree that our social, economical and political system is rigged. From school to workplace, the two faced appropriate conversation is filled with inappropriate intentions. No problem can be solved without first acknowledging the existence of problem and intent to be resolved. The real toxicity exist inside the subculture where appropriateness is the protective layer. Radical change would mean to break the wall of appropriateness in order to identify, expose and eradicate the subculture.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Rest in Peace NDP Labour Party</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/rest-in-peace-ndp-labour-party/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/rest-in-peace-ndp-labour-party/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
New Democratic Party of Canada (NDP) represented more than 85 percent of Canadians who were wage earners in the country. The orange colour even visible at night became a household symbol in early 1960 when workers were building the country after double world wars.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Bollywood Politics to Real Democracy</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/bollywood-politics-to-real-democracy/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/bollywood-politics-to-real-democracy/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
During the free fall of British Empire, the visionary Mahatma Gandhi helped liberate India from the British colonizer in 1947. After 70 years of democracy, India is yet to find a place on the map other than population statistics. Imperial socialist China was able to lift Chinese out of the darkness utilizing the greed of American corporations. While the hostile nature of big American corporations continue to bring enormous opportunity to India; India’s ability to harvest the greed would dictate the future.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Canada Get Out of NATO War Machine</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/canada-get-out-of-nato-war-machine/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/canada-get-out-of-nato-war-machine/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Real solution to the Ukraine Russia war is on the table; yet, ruling class of all NATO nations are advocating for war. For instance, sending weapons to conflict zone under the banner of peace and democracy is the perfect irony of all.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>God is in the Details</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/god-is-in-the-details/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/god-is-in-the-details/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
As they say, devil is in the details so do god. Our social pragmatics fail at the interpretation of god, miserably. The path to heaven paved with misinterpretation to false preaching and skewed perspective of the creator. No spiritual journey can be accomplished without right information at disposal. People united can never be defeated; that is the real insecurity of all power that intend to keep everyone divided.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Apologies to Freedom Convey Canada</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/apologies-to-freedom-convey-canada/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/apologies-to-freedom-convey-canada/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
As a left wing activist, I joined the mainstream narrative to discredit the legitimate concerns of the freedom convey movement. I am offended at my stupidity and regret my actions. I want to say that I am really sorry to all those I treated with disrespect for not taking vaccinations. Indeed, I was mocking at the people who were defending my interest.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Thinking Process of Political Hierarchy</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/thinking-process-of-political-hierarchy/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/thinking-process-of-political-hierarchy/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The war between Ukraine and Russia helps analyze the thinking process of social class in modern society. The actual winners and losers of warfare can be understood through the lens of owner class, ruling class and working class. Owner class does not fight any battle but reaps all the benefits of conflicts. Those who own shares in weapon industry can be classified as the owner class.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Exploring Social Class in Warfare</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/exploring-social-class-in-warfare/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/exploring-social-class-in-warfare/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
All wars are evil expression of human kind. The military complex of any nation is a well organized and operated structure of destruction employing modern weapons and trained to kill combatants. A relentless of pursuit of worst of humanity can achieve disguised as protection of civilization.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Deception is Disgust; Not Intelligence</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/deception-is-disgust-not-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/deception-is-disgust-not-intelligence/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Deception is an action of deceiving someone for one’s benefit. Historically, legal system is created to make sure those cannot speak to have their voices heard and rights protected. Today, justice system is built on deception to protect the criminals; hence, criminal justice system.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Rapid Rise of Fascism in India</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-rapid-rise-of-fascism-in-india/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-rapid-rise-of-fascism-in-india/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Unlike what is believed to be, Hinduism is not a religion, it is a way of life. Eventually, the practice of Hinduism became a disciplined religion. Not only Hinduism is the oldest religion in the world but many advancement of modern civilization roots back to Hindu way of life.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>White Advantage of the Holocaust</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/white-advantage-of-the-holocaust/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/white-advantage-of-the-holocaust/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
When apartheid Israel restricted Ukraine refugees fleeing war, the inhumane decision not only received international condemnation but also encouraged to revisit the era of holocaust.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Reality of How People Get Rich</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/reality-of-how-people-get-rich/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/reality-of-how-people-get-rich/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The perspective of how people get rich is completely misunderstood but no one wants to challenge the norm. Statistically, an average person cannot work to become millionaire; yet, we believe the false narrative because it feels good.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Human Rights if You Can Afford</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/human-rights-if-you-can-afford/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/human-rights-if-you-can-afford/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
If human rights whether employment, housing or any in Ontario, do not waste time with Ontario Human Rights Tribunal (OHRT). The best solution is to go public if you can and join a movement. OHRT exist to protect the interest of the political party in power, not your human rights. They are appointed through elected government to play the game according to instructions.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What is Hypocrisy in Social Media?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/what-is-hypocrisy-in-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/what-is-hypocrisy-in-social-media/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Hypocrisy is the practice of claiming to have higher standards or more noble believes than is the case. Simply put, a self serving false believe system of positive, negative and neutral positions. Often, hypocrisy goes unchallenged but closely associated with lies and rumours.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Racism in Modern Policing Culture</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/racism-in-modern-policing-culture/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/racism-in-modern-policing-culture/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The woman who works as cashier to earn minimum wage in order to feed the kid that police view as criminal is set to struggle; not overcome. If Toronto Police really care about the well being of women lead families, do the right thing, stop treating blacks and minority as criminals.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Real Definition of &#39;Under Developed&#39; Phrase</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/real-definition-of-under-developed-phrase/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/real-definition-of-under-developed-phrase/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The term “developed” to describe Europe and North American countries undermine the human advancement in Asia, Middle East and African countries. Due to repeat colonization and wars, those countries did not have the opportunity to protect the development or advance civilization. To use the word “developing” without accompanying exploitation is an act of discrimination.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Mutation of Toxic Racism in Ukraine Crisis</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/mutation-of-toxic-racism-in-ukraine-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/mutation-of-toxic-racism-in-ukraine-crisis/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
According to Oxford, racism is a prejudice, discrimination or antagonism directed against someone of a different race based on the belief that one’s own race is superior.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What is the Nature of Zionism?</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/what-is-the-nature-of-zionism/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/what-is-the-nature-of-zionism/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Anti-Semitism is a law that protect Jewish people against hate crimes. When we oppose zionism and apartheid, we must be clear not to prejudice Jewish people. Indeed, most Jewish people are oppose to zionism and apartheid but refrain from speaking out due to repercussions from their own kind.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Root of All Conflicts ‘Apartheid’</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/root-of-all-conflicts-apartheid/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/root-of-all-conflicts-apartheid/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Apartheid is the Afrikaans word for ‘apartness’, originally used to describe the system of racial discrimination that existed in South Africa until 1994. The term apartheid is not only a reference to South Africa’s former regime; it is used in international law to describe a category of regime, defined in the United Nations (UN) International Convention on the Suppression and Punishment of the Crime of Apartheid (1973), to which more than 100 states are a party.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Rise of Palestine Against Apartheid State</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/rise-of-palestine-against-apartheid-state/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/rise-of-palestine-against-apartheid-state/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
When apartheid state is getting caught with pants down, I am not complaining. Viva viva Palestine. Kudos to the Irish MP Richard Boyd Barrett exposing the crimes.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Demons of Peace - Sri Lanka to Ukraine</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/demons-of-peace-sri-lanka-to-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/demons-of-peace-sri-lanka-to-ukraine/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
In 1947, when the last colonizer British left Ceylon, they handed the power over to the majority of the country. The majority 85% were Sinhalese while less than 15% were Tamils. British favoured Tamils over the majority Sinhalese to lead the country for variety of reasons; however, abruptly left without any framework to run the country with 20 million people. During British occupation, Tamils enjoyed close connections to British administrations and were employed in high ranking roles. That embroiled bitter taste in the majority Sinhalese administrations. The ring wing Sinhalese majority seized power and began crushing the Tamil minority through all legal means to make Tamils secondary citizens.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Believe the Lies to Avoid Prison</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/believe-the-lies-to-avoid-prison/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/believe-the-lies-to-avoid-prison/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Western media hypocrisy has reached new levels. No one is allowed to speak the truth, if you do, expect to be labelled Russian or communist. It beg the question, what is wrong with Russian or communism? If a communist nation was able to defeat the Hitler Nazis, they must have something better than what capitalism offers.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Politics of Divide and Conquer</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-politics-of-divide-and-conquer/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-politics-of-divide-and-conquer/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Racism exists because we accept racist standards. Due to imbalance of power, the oppressed cannot challenge the oppressor. After 2000 years, we still have government officials in Poland not shamed to admit racist decisions that were used to deny muslims and African refugees of Ukraine. The ruling class does very little to address racism because division and conquer is the pillars of modern politics. Do we need a class war to free all those oppressed?

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Hidden Agenda of Ukraine Crisis</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/hidden-agenda-of-ukraine-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/hidden-agenda-of-ukraine-crisis/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
After failing to stop Russia from invading Ukraine, the western countries and their media outlets have unleashed a propaganda war that involves sharing old pictures from past conflicts to demonise Russia and lavishing praises on Ukrainian leadership for standing its ground against the invasion, seemingly to paper over their own inadequacies.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Victims of Lies, Deception and Cruelty</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/victims-of-lies-deception-and-cruelty/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/victims-of-lies-deception-and-cruelty/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
What we know is very little compared to what we do not know. Without COVID and Putin, we may never have known the real face of our corporate media, government and the lies. The pandemic driven social awakening was elegantly silenced through redistributing hate against Russia. Without corporate media support and the black suites, our capitalist government would be illegitimate.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Cash Cow in Action</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-cash-cow-in-action/"/>
        <updated>2021-03-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-cash-cow-in-action/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Over the years, public distrust in our government and big corporations was declining at a rapid rate. As always, elected governments were not representing the majority; instead, advocated for the agenda of the elites and the few at the top. Meanwhile workers were left to die at the frontline to earn poverty wages; squeezed between high cost of food and greedy bankers.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Hypocrisy OUT, Democracy IN</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/hypocrisy-out-democracy-in/"/>
        <updated>2021-02-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/hypocrisy-out-democracy-in/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
European Commission sending weapons to Ukraine instead of peace and Israel endorsing the Nazi party are the pinnacle of any hypocrisy can reach.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Stand with Ukraine People; Not NATO</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/stand-with-ukraine-people-not-nato/"/>
        <updated>2021-02-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/stand-with-ukraine-people-not-nato/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
No war is good except class war. However, we do not always get to hear the full story in the mainstream media. Our corporate media and elites have an agenda that undermine our democracy and wellbeing of everyone except rulers and corporates.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Double Standards of Heroism in Hypocrisy</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/double-standards-of-heroism-in-hypocrisy/"/>
        <updated>2021-02-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/double-standards-of-heroism-in-hypocrisy/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
So if you fight your freedom in Ukraine, you are hero but if you do the same in Palestine, you are a terrorist. We need to find out who is setting the standards.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Some Children are More Important</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/some-children-are-more-important/"/>
        <updated>2021-02-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/some-children-are-more-important/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Before you reserve all your sympathy to children of Ukraine, please know that 67 innocent Palestinian children slaughtered by the Israeli bombing of Gaza last May, but no sanctions: nothing but a handshake. Clearly, they do not look like terrorists. Why are they not important?

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Greatest Failures of Human Civilization</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/greatest-failures-of-human-civilization/"/>
        <updated>2021-02-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/greatest-failures-of-human-civilization/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The bankers will ensure we stay in debt. The pharmaceutical companies will ensure we stay sick. The weapons manufacturers will ensure we keep going to war. The media will ensure we are prevented from knowing the truth. The government will ensure all of this is done legally. Sad.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Ruling Class, Far Greater Threat</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/ruling-class-far-greater-threat/"/>
        <updated>2021-02-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/ruling-class-far-greater-threat/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
There’s no gentle way to say it, but the truth is that a lot of us hate our elites far more than we hate some foreign dictator because ruling class is far greater threat to Canada and the United States than a foreign dictator.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Canadians are Not Totalitarians Joe</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/canadians-are-not-totalitarians-joe/"/>
        <updated>2021-02-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/canadians-are-not-totalitarians-joe/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Of course Canada is in the centre stage in the global media for unpleasant reasons. Most corporate media will do whatever necessary to amplify the freedom convey issues. Those who live outside the Canadian borders believe Canadian truckers are fighting for better employment, wages and benefits but we know that is far from reality.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Left and Right to Connect the Dots</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/left-and-right-to-connect-the-dots/"/>
        <updated>2021-02-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/left-and-right-to-connect-the-dots/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The left and the right connect the dots. We can build back better but not this way. It is not democracy, equality or justice. Absolute fascism and plain dictatorship of political dissents. The famous line, &quot;We were just following the orders&quot;.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Pandemic Story of Workers</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-pandemic-story-of-workers/"/>
        <updated>2021-02-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-pandemic-story-of-workers/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Life was not fair to workers even before the pandemic. We worked multiple jobs to feed and pay rent so few can get rich when food and shelter was a basic human need. As a frontline employee, I paid my dues while billionaires were going to space and laugh at us on their way back during the lock-down. Our capitalist leaders were protecting the big corporations while people were dying of disease that was manufactured through greed, ignorance and cruelty to humanity.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Zionist Devil Consume Palestine Lands</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/zionist-devil-consume-palestine-lands/"/>
        <updated>2020-06-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/zionist-devil-consume-palestine-lands/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The Palestine Israel conflict began since creation of Israel in the occupied land of Palestine. Zionist Israel used all evil means to divide humanity and control freedom of speech to achieve a false democracy. There is no freedom of speech or freedom to move for those who disapprove the genocide of Palestine people. People of Israel are victim of political propaganda to accept the genocide of Palestine while reject holocaust. If terrorization of Palestine people is justified, why so much outcry about gas chambers?

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Tamil Genocide by Sri Lanka</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-tamil-genocide-by-sri-lanka/"/>
        <updated>2020-05-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/the-tamil-genocide-by-sri-lanka/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Sri Lanka’s government declared victory in May, 2009, in one of the world’s most intractable wars after a series of battles in which it killed the leader of the Tamil Tigers, who had been fighting to create a separate homeland for the country’s ethnic Tamil minority. The United Nations said the conflict had killed between 80,000 and 100,000 people in Sri Lanka since full-scale civil war broke out in 1983. The global failure to protect Tamil rights under International Law and the extraordinary silence of the Holocaust survivers must be questioned.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Tabor Hill Scarborough, Feast of the Dead</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/tabor-hill-scarborough-feast-of-the-dead/"/>
        <updated>2020-04-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/tabor-hill-scarborough-feast-of-the-dead/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
In Scarborough, the Tabor Hill Site is the most well known archeological site. This section will refocus our attention to an important moment in Scarborough history and outcomes of the excavation conducted by archaeologist Walter Kenyon. Under the scholarship of University of Toronto Professor Walter Kenyon, an Indigenous burial site dating to the 13th century was discovered. Excerpt from Scarborough Historical Society.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Canadian Garbage Trapped in Philippines</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/canadian-garbage-trapped-in-philippines/"/>
        <updated>2020-03-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/canadian-garbage-trapped-in-philippines/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
The Canadian containers arrived in the Philippines in 2013 and 2014 falsely labelled as being full of recycling plastics. Philippine customs authorities inspected the containers and discovered about two-thirds of them to be ordinary household garbage, including electronic waste and used diapers.

</content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Mullivaikkal Massacre in May 2009</title>
        <link href="https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/mullivaikkal-massacre-in-may-2009/"/>
        <updated>2020-03-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://kiri-vadivelu.ca/blog/mullivaikkal-massacre-in-may-2009/</id>
        
        <content type="html">
Of course, International courts headed by United States and the apartheid Israel did not have enough evidence to prove genocide or use of chemical weapons during the final phase of War in Sri Lanka. A classic conclusion of court case in a corporate capitalist society where money talks bullshit walks. Please exercise caution before viewing the images as they may be extremely disturbing to some.

</content>
    </entry></feed>